[
    {
        "questiontext": "In Gravesend, England, there is a whole fake town used by police to simulate * situations.",
        "correctanswer": "dangerous",
        "fakeanswers": "stressing, boring, funny, surprising"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Japan har strawberries called *, that are completely white inside and out, with red seeds.",
        "correctanswer": "Scent of First Love"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "A Japanese zoo unsuccessfully tried to mate a pair of hyenas for four years, before realizing that both were *.",
        "correctanswer": "male",
        "fakeanswers": "Old, Sterile, Female"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "In 2010, photographer Robert B. Haas captured a unique photo of a flock of flamingos gathered in the shape of *.",
        "correctanswer": "a flamingo"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "The first president of Zimbabwe was called \"President *\".",
        "correctanswer": "Banana"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "A swedish man survived for two months in a car that had been snowed over. He ate only *, and survived due to an \"igloo-effect\".",
        "correctanswer": "snow"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Alpacas, unlike most other animals, can die of *.",
        "correctanswer": "loneliness"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "If Britain were a US state, it would be the second *, behind Alabama and before Mississippi.",
        "correctanswer": "poorest"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "40 million people in China live in *.",
        "correctanswer": "caves"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Koko, a female gorilla trained in sign language, once tore a steel sink out of it's moorings. When her handlers confronted her, Koko signed \"*\".",
        "correctanswer": "cat did it"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Couples that cuddle can become * to one another.",
        "correctanswer": "addicted"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Male kangaroos show off their * to impress females.",
        "correctanswer": "biceps"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "About 25% of all Russian men die before they reach their mid-50s, mainly due to *.",
        "correctanswer": "vodka"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Napoleon Bonaparte was buried with all parts of his body, except one: *",
        "correctanswer": "his penis"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "The state of finding it hard to get out of bed in the morning.",
        "correctanswer": "dysania"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Holding money in your hand can reduce *",
        "correctanswer": "stress"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Iran once tried to get into Guinness book of world records by making the  world's biggest *",
        "correctanswer": "sandwich"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Touching stainless steel will remove the odor of * from your hands.",
        "correctanswer": "garlic"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "In 2014, * surpassed car crashes as the leading cause of accidental  deaths in the US.",
        "correctanswer": "prescription drugs"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "What did the last man to be executed by a firing squad in the US as for as his last wish?",
        "correctanswer": "a bulletproof vest"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "NYC homeowners can request that a * be placed outside their home for free.",
        "correctanswer": "tree"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "There are no * in Las Vegas casinos.",
        "correctanswer": "clocks"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "A * mania caused the death of several people in Strasbourg in 1518.",
        "correctanswer": "dancing"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Applying a male's * to a female's lips can help women relax, boost their mood, and help regulate their menstrual cycle.",
        "correctanswer": "underarm sweat"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "When a male honeybee climaxes during sex, his testicles *.",
        "correctanswer": "explode"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Technically speaking, a female \"dude\" is a *.",
        "correctanswer": "dudine"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "The only food that never goes bad is *.",
        "correctanswer": "honey"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Dragonflies have *-shaped penises.",
        "correctanswer": "shovel"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Female kangaroos have three *.",
        "correctanswer": "vaginas"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "What was the real middle name of US president Harry S. Truman?",
        "correctanswer": "S"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "Casu marzu is a Sardinian cheese that contains *",
        "correctanswer": "live maggots"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "There are towns in France where it is illegal to *.",
        "correctanswer": "die"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "There are pills that make your farts smell like '.",
        "correctanswer": "roses"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "In the middle ages, people thought farting in jars and then sniffing them would prevent *",
        "correctanswer": "death"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "The Mongolian Death Worm can grow to be 5 feet long, and it kills its prey with *.",
        "correctanswer": "electric shocks from its eyes"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "In 1962, the Tanganyikan village of Kashasha was the victim of a year-long * epidemic.",
        "correctanswer": "laughter"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "There are depictions of medieval knights fighting * in ancient manuscripts,and nobody knows why.",
        "correctanswer": "snails"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "In Japan, it is illegal to * after midnight.",
        "correctanswer": "dance",
        "fakeanswers": "feed gremlins"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "* can be hired to stalk your child for a week before their birthday.",
        "correctanswer": "evil clowns"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "The month of May is officially celebrated as \"* Awareness Month\" in the US.",
        "correctanswer": "zombie"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "If police officers in Thailand break the law, they are forced to wear armbands featuring *",
        "correctanswer": "Hello Kitty"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "In 1995 in North America, a man became a local celebrity just because his name was \"*\".",
        "correctanswer": "Dick Assman"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "In Oklahoma, it is illegal to take a bite out of someone else's *",
        "correctanswer": "hamburger"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "The more attracted you are to someone, the easier it is for them to make you *.",
        "correctanswer": "laugh"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "A man once sued his wife for being *, and won.",
        "correctanswer": "ugly"
    },
    {
        "questiontext": "There is a hand sanitizer called \"Maybe you touched *\"",
        "correctanswer": "your genitals"
    }
]